<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: foss | [Blog Title Here]]]></title>
  <link href="http://waterphox.github.com/blog/categories/foss/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://waterphox.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-04-10T02:17:25+04:00</updated>
  <id>http://waterphox.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Waterfox]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learning Python so I can be Sweet]]></title>
    <link href="http://waterphox.github.com/blog/2013/04/10/learning-python-so-i-can-be-sweet/"/>
    <updated>2013-04-10T02:03:00+04:00</updated>
    <id>http://waterphox.github.com/blog/2013/04/10/learning-python-so-i-can-be-sweet</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Hrmm, I should have posted a bunch more before this.
Since posting about Sugar Activities I have been trying to acquaint myself with python.
We've also made some headway on Sweetermail, which is what we've named our XOmail furthering project,
I haven't been able to help much, due to lack of python experience; but with the python practise I can at least understand the source code now.
It seemed like learning python would not be such a daunting task, but now http://trypython.org is giving 503 errors. :/</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Links:
Sweetermail: https://github.com/FOSSRIT/sweetermail
Python Interactive Tutorial: http://trypython.org</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Interesting Sugar Labs Activities]]></title>
    <link href="http://waterphox.github.com/blog/2013/03/15/interesting-sugar-labs-activities/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-15T01:29:00+04:00</updated>
    <id>http://waterphox.github.com/blog/2013/03/15/interesting-sugar-labs-activities</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I perused the activities pages of the Sugar Labs site and picked a few activities I thought were interesting.
Physics, Jam GBA Emulator, and Kiwix.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Physics is interesting because it is somewhat like another game I enjoy immensely, Phun. There are less options than Phun, but the core "make objects that bounce around with physical properties" thing is still there.</p>

<p>As the XOs have little Gameboy-like buttons on them, I figured a GBA emulator would be perfect. I can't wait to fold the screen down and try playing Rhythm Tengoku!</p>

<p>Lastly, Kiwix is an offline Wikipedia reader. I like the idea of that because the environments XOs are intended for may not always have an internet connection. After downloading pre-packaged pages to Kiwix, there will be lots of available reading on the XO. You know how it is with Wikipedia, a few clicks and you're reading for hours.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
