<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[[Blog Title Here]]]></title>
  <link href="http://waterphox.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://waterphox.github.com/"/>
  <updated>2013-03-06T20:30:16+04:00</updated>
  <id>http://waterphox.github.com/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Waterfox]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[What are you doing]]></title>
    <link href="http://waterphox.github.com/blog/2013/03/06/what-are-you-doing/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-06T19:48:00+04:00</updated>
    <id>http://waterphox.github.com/blog/2013/03/06/what-are-you-doing</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>World, you&#8217;re totally cray.
Cray cray.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray
Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray Cray</p>

<p>Mmk.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello]]></title>
    <link href="http://waterphox.github.com/blog/2013/03/06/hello/"/>
    <updated>2013-03-06T19:07:00+04:00</updated>
    <id>http://waterphox.github.com/blog/2013/03/06/hello</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>If this is visible, it means the blog works. Yay.
If it&#8217;s not.. crap.</p>

<!-- more -->


<p>Mmk.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
